Wealth, Fame, Power.
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer,
and his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
You want my treasure?
You can have it.
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it.
These words lured men to
the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they'd ever dared to imagine.
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era.
Come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams.
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for.
One piece.
Compass left behind,
it'll only slow us down.
Your heart will be your guide,
raise the sails and take the helm.
That legendary place that
the end of the map reveals.
Is only legendary until
someone proves it real.
Through it all, through
all the trouble of times.
Through the heartache
and through the pain.
Know that I will be there to stand by you.
Just like I know you'll stand by me.
So come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams.
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for.
There's always room for you
if you want to be my friend.
We are, we are on a cruise.
We are.
Okay, at daybreak, the pirates will be
landing at this shore to begin their attack!
But the only way they'll be able to get
to the village is to go up this slope.
The rest of the shoreline is sheer
cliffs, so they have to come through here.
If we can fight them while they're
funneled into that narrow pass,
their numbers won't mean anything
and the village will be protected.
Alright, sounds pretty easy!
Talking about it is, but
victory depends on our strength.
What is it you guys can do?
I cut.
I stretch. I steal.
I hide.
Well, there's no way better to fight!
Just make it up funny!
Come on, calm down!
Ah, Klahadore, welcome back. How is she?
She's resting just now.
She was quite exhausted.
I leave town for a few hours
to tend to some errands,
and everything falls to pieces.
That Usopp certainly knows how
to cause trouble, doesn't he?
Yes.
And on top of everything else he's done
today, he claimed you were a pirate.
I can't think of a more outrageous lie.
Indeed.
What's this here?
Well, that's a present, of course,
from Miss Kaya to you, Klahadore.
It's been three years since
you came to this mansion,
and this gift is to say
thank you for your hard work.
It's a commemoration of sorts. How nice.
The glasses you're wearing are always
slipping and you have to push them back up.
So the lady of the house custom
ordered a new pair for you.
Isn't she just the most thoughtful
young woman you've ever met?
How appropriate.
Tomorrow will be a day
worth commemorating.
It's a crescent moon tonight.
Huh?
It's on nights like these
that I truly feel alive.
My heart races and my
blood boils in my veins.
Clorador, what are you doing?
Why would you do such a
thing to Miss Kaya's present?
Oh, I'll be receiving a gift, all right.
But it won't be glasses.
It'll be her entire estate. Oh!
What are you saying?
I suppose there's no reason to
carry on the act any longer.
In a few hours, the village will
be mourning the unforeseen tragedy.
Three long years I've
quietly waited for this.
Miss!
You have to get out of here!
Run!
Captain Django!
Captain Django, it's almost daybreak.
It's time to get moving.
Good morning, Captain.
Good morning, sir.
You idiot.
Only the sun can wake me up
and live to tell about it.
Do I make myself clear?
He's in a really bad mood.
Mornings are the worst. Just look.
The moon is still up, so the
sun couldn't have woken me.
Now, which one of you did it?
No apologies, sir.
We're very sorry, sir.
Good morning, gentlemen.
Wait, what's going on here?
He was mad just a second ago.
So what?
He's in a better mood now, and that's all
that matters, so keep your big trap shut.
Attention, men.
Let's set sail!
Yep, I'm a genius.
There's no way they'll be able
to make it up this slope now.
All this oil we put here should keep them
occupied while we go to work on them.
They're going to be busy slipping and
sliding around like a bunch of idiots,
and we show up and beat
the crap out of them.
Wow, so that's your plan, huh?
That's right.
I'm going to defend the village
no matter what it takes.
Let's just hope none of us slip on that
oil and end up down there with them,
because that would be like
sliding into a meat grinder.
Usopp, I gotta hand it to you.
You're pretty good at fighting dirty.
Of course I am!
There isn't anyone alive
who can best me with a
slingshot or beat me at
the art of fighting dirty!
It's almost daybreak.
They're coming.
We're here!
All right, men.
You know what to do.
Go ashore, crash the village,
head for the mansion.
Aye, sir!
Captain, there are already
two boats here. What?
Shall I investigate?
Leave them for later.
They don't look like treasure ships to
me, and we have a schedule to keep...
Where are they?
We were gonna fight the
sun's up. What's the deal?
Oh, maybe they overslept
Wait a minute, maybe I'm hearing things,
but it sounds like battle
cries from somewhere?
Yeah, I definitely hear them!
No, it can't be, what can't be?
And there's a shore just
like this to the north.
They went
We're at the wrong shore.
It's not good.
Well, this is where they
had their secret meeting.
So I just assumed, okay
We need to hurry before
they make it to the village.
Where is it?
You have to head directly north
from here if you run you can make
it in three minutes the terrain
there is almost exactly the same.
So all we need to do is
stop them at the slope?
Oh, no!
If those filthy pirates are at the North
Shore, then they've already seen our boats!
They'll take our treasure!
I'll be there in 20 seconds! Oh, man!
My brilliant oil strategy
was all for nothing!
My precious treasure...
Hey, what are you doing?
Let's get out of here.
Yeah!
Help!
I'm gonna fall!
Let go, you moron! Sorry!
Hello.
See you there.
Sorry, but you understand
the treasure's in danger.
That oil won't be a
problem for you, right?
That girl's gonna pay.
I swear all my life they'll
never set foot in my village.
That Luffy sure has a good runner.
He's so far ahead, I can't
even see him anymore.
Run straight north!
Those mongrels are in big trouble if
they so much as look at my treasure!
It's an ambush!
Somebody's up there!
We meet again.
I am the legendary Captain Usopp!
I've been waiting for you!
I wasn't supposed to
be the first one here!
He was running way ahead of me!
I can't handle these guys alone!
Crap!
How am I supposed to get past this stuff?
The village!
That can't be right.
He said run north, and I ran in a coldish
direction, so I should be at the shore.
It's you. I remember.
You're one of the troublesome
brats who overheard our plan.
What do you think you're doing?
I'm warning you!
Leave here while you still can!
If you don't, my 100 million
crewmen will massacre all of you!
One hundred million?
Are we really supposed
to believe that? No way!
One hundred million?
Incredible!
Captain, he's obviously lying.
Then it's time to call his bluff.
They saw through it.
That guy seriously thought he
could fool us. What's that?
You've been lying to us this whole time?
Captain Jango, take a look at this.
Oh, no, is it bad?
No, sir, it's good.
We searched those other ships and
found a huge load of treasure.
It's hard to say how much, but I bet
it's around five million berries.
What?
Five million berries?
How in the world did those guys
get a hold of so much treasure?
I see you found my loot.
Well, you can have it.
You're just gonna let
us take your treasure?
That's right.
Just turn around and forget all about
this place, and the treasure is yours.
I didn't think people that
stupid actually existed.
At this point, he's just
embarrassing himself.
Okay, do you know what a pirate is?
We're going to take this treasure, and
there's nothing you can do about it.
And there is no way we're turning
back until we get where we came for.
Well, yeah, that makes sense.
All right, then.
On the count of one, two,
Jango, you'll let us by.
It's that strange weapon from before.
One, two...
Don't you ever try to get
my heart and treasure away!
My head!
Hey, who is this crazy girl?
Captain, this isn't the time
to be hypnotizing yourself.
We got a mission to carry out, remember?
That treasure boat is mine, and I'm not
going to let you have a single bearing.
Do you hear me?
In fact, you better clear out, because
I'm coming down there to get it back!
That really hurts!
Who said you could give them my treasure?
You got what you deserve!
I didn't give them the treasure.
I just said I would give it to them.
That's the same thing, and
I just saved your life.
Huh?
I guess I forgot to
mention it to you earlier.
Don't ever watch his ring routine.
That weirdo's a hypnotist.
Hypnotist?
So where's Luffy?
He's a fast runner.
I thought he'd be here way ahead of you.
I don't know.
He either got lost or he
chickened out at the last minute.
The only thing that could keep
him from a fight is getting lost.
Right when we need him, too.
I'll go ahead and take command here.
I think it's about time you
go and kick their butts.
What? Me?
What about you?
I can't take on a boatload
of vicious pirates by myself.
That's just suicide.
What, like I'm gonna do any fighting?
Beneath this calm exterior lies
the abject terror of a coward.
Oh, so you think you're scared?
Well, I'm so scared I am
literally about to cry.
Please, your eyes are completely dry.
You'll have to do better than that.
Liars can smell their own.
That's just your upper lip.
I got beat up by...
We don't have time for this nonsense.
All right, men, let's get to work.
Crush them and move to the village.
Here they come.
Wait, I know.
I have some Caltrups.
Those are just what the doctor ordered.
Let me have some.
You're gonna love this.
Caltrups! Help!
Nami, if you're still alive when I
get out of here, I'm gonna kill you!
Take that oil!
Now, how do I get to the
north shore from here?
Run straight north!
Which way is north?
Yes! We got him! Check it out! Here comes!
The lead star!
Bastard. Way to go.
You're quite the warrior after all.
Looks like you got this handled,
so I'll just take a break.
But you haven't done anything yet!
What is it?
There are caltrops behind us.
Idiot!
You dropped those things behind us, too?
Get out of the way!
Ha!
Don't tell me you really thought you
were going to stop us down there!
Let's go, fellas!
Captain Kuro hates waiting!
You again?
Let go of me, you jackass!
You want some more?
Here, have some!
Have a little more!
I will never...
let you step foot in that village!
All I did was lie like I always do.
See, today will be like every other
day in that sleepy little town.
Cause you and your cronies
will never set foot in it!
Shots?
Stupid girls?
Treasure.
Are you?
Shut up I won't tell you again!
We've wasted enough time playing pirates!
Quit bothering with him
and move to the village!
Or have you forgotten that this
is Captain Kuro's operation,
and he doesn't look favorably on his
well-laid plans being ruined by idiots?
He'll kill us all!
Do you understand that, you cretins?
He's right! Yeah!
Let's get to the village!
Don't go any further!
I said stop!
Turn back.
Don't take another step. Get off me!
Please don't kill them.
Just leave this village alone.
They're good people.
They don't deserve this.
I love this place. Please.
What is this, Captain Django?
Nobody told us that killers like
those were going to be here!
It's about time.
Is that the best those
pirates can dish out?
Yeah, I was hoping for a challenge.
And you!
After leaving me down there, you're
lucky I'm not kicking your butt, too!
Usopp, you big bonehead!
You never told me which
direction was north!
Who are these guys?
They're late.
I don't appreciate tardiness, not one bit.
They know full well what happens to those
who are foolish enough to upset my plans.
Do they think they can
take their sweet time?
Well, if they have forgotten the
consequences of disappointing me,
I'll kill them all.
Wow!
That was great!
You guys are really that strong?
Mm-hmm.
Could you have been slower?
What took you so long?
You're the one who pushed me down
that oil slick so you could get out.
It was an accident.
I slipped, you fell.
At least one of us made it out of there.
That's better than both of
us being stuck at the bottom.
It should have just been you!
Run straight north, he says.
That's just great.
I mean, how am I supposed to know
which way north even is out here, huh?
Shut up.
You're the one who ran away so sure
of yourself, ready to take on anyone.
I just got so excited, I
started running, you know?
The sun rises high in the sky now, and that
means Captain Kuro goes very impatient.
Men, don't just lie there.
You can't tell me you're
going to let them win.
They're just a couple of idiots.
The fact is, we don't have time to
lollygag around here any longer.
If our enemy is strong, then we
must become stronger than them.
Here stare deeply into this ring now!
I will count one to jungle and after
that you will all begin to grow stronger.
Your wounds will heal and you will grow
stronger still so what is he doing?
It looks weird Looks like hypnosis.
He's trying to convince them.
They're stronger than they
are like that'll work one
true
No way!
That one guy completely
destroyed the cliff!
Now that's what I call power!
I always thought hypnotizing
people was a bunch of crap!
That was just one of them!
Imagine what the whole crew can do!
Now go, and strike down
all who stand in your way!
Hey, you guys, you might want to move.
Luffy, you and I will take it from here.
All right, then.
What now?
Uh, Luffy?
Don't tell me you let that
freak hypnotize you too!
Oh, he really is a simple-minded idiot!
Damn you, Captain Kuro, you made
one hell of a miscalculation.
These are not your average village idiots.
Where's he going?
What is he doing?
That's right!
Tear it down!
He's going to destroy our ship!
Oh no, he's gonna crush
us with it, everybody run!
Run!
Captain, do something!
One, two, jungle, you will fall asleep!
One, two, jungle!
Ahhhh!
Looks like those guys are probably
down for the count, don't you think?
I guess.
Maybe.
But Luffy's still trapped
underneath that cat.
Just look.
Relax, he's fine.
You should really worry about your
own injuries by the looks of it.
Damn that little brat.
Now our whole plan's shot to hell.
What am I gonna do with this mess?
Captain Kuro sees this and he'll kill us!
Poochie, come check this out!
There's some bad stuff going down!
What the hell?
I forgot we still have our trump card.
Come forth!
Meowban brothers!
It looks like the butler
from Kaia's mansion.
But it's so early in the morning.
Why is he walking to the shore?
Was in my grasp.
And I wouldn't let go.
La la la la.
My only dream.
La la la la la.
I won't stop chasing it!
Until it comes true.
But if the world ever changes?
I call out your name.
We return to the time when
everything's the same.
As long as I'm with you,
my memories won't fade.
Waiting for that one true dream?